[{"answer": "I think it's very obvious, Piers, and that's jobs and the economy.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "What is the real strategy at this stage of the battle plan that you think he needs to be most aware of?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Well, probably the same impression that people have when they show Hillary Clinton saying, \"Shame on you, Barack Obama.\"", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "How much of a problem is it going to be if Barack Obama begins replaying that criticism and indeed from other senior Republicans to say, come on, even you guys didn't think he was that great?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "You know, the problem with the free enterprise system is that not everybody succeeds.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "Or as some other people say, look, it's fine, he did create jobs, but he also wrecked a lot of jobs?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, let me put this in context.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Why doesn't he just do it?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Of course not.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "But just to clarify, you never saw anything that you think would cause him embarrassment?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "Chicago style means that there's very few depths you won't plummet.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "What does Chicago-style mean?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "I have not seen anyone accused of possibly being a felon.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Seriously, the lowest you've ever seen?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Well, your point is well made in this respect.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "I'm not sure you can do that kind of campaign and then honestly stand back and go, come on, you're not being fair to me, can you?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "What we should have done a long time ago was join with other nations and set up a safe zone and together provide arms and equipment to the resistance fighters who are being massacred.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "What should be done about this?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Yes, and one of the sad aspects of this, he doesn't even speak up on these people's behalf.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Is it time that President Obama did something?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "I've met them in a refugee camps.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "And you've met some of these people?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "I say that's true but I also think that there's a variety of reasons, including a polarization amongst the American people.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "What do you say to that charge?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "I think that it's a very unique interpretation of the real world to say that money is speech.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "The fundamental principle is that it bring -- it does not rein in any way the activities of the labor unions.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "What is the fundamental principle issue here that you object to?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "You would sign up for that?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "I say I never left.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "How do you feel when people say, we've got the real John McCain?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "I don't know --", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Would you like Michele Bachmann to apologize?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "I don't know what she should do.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "-- in particular?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Listen, we just had a sheriff of Maricopa County, again, who has taken it upon himself to prove that President Obama was not born in the United States of America.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "What does it say about the state of modern politics, that that kind of thing can happen?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "It's crazy.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Well, I think you need to say one thing more, which is what does it tell you about the state of politics?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "It is day by day.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "What goes through the mind of a wife in this situation?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Yeah, its exhilarating.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "Was that your memory of it?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "Oh, no.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "Do you actually regret -- if you're honest, do you look in the mirror and regret at least going for it?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "CCAIN: Well, it's not that it could or couldn't have.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "It could have worked?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "I was proud of my ability to resist all kinds of pressures from my captors, both mental and physical.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "When you were in Vietnam, and you went through five, six years of absolute hell, repeated tortures, beatings, so on, what did you learn about yourself that has now dictated the way you are as a politician?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Probably the day I left prison.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "If I could relive -- outside marriage and children, if I could have the power to let you relieve five minutes of your live, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Yes, I don't disagree with him at all.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "Do you agree with him?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "I don't think we know enough about the opposition yet.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "I mean, do they have a point?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Yeah, that's an interesting point.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "When would the military possibly turn on Assad?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "I saw that attack as an indicator of what I see as the era that we're in.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "And what should be done about it?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Did you feel optimism there?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "This is an issue that we in the military have been working very hard for years.", "docId": "120719pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Why is this happening and what can be done about it?", "qSentId": 537}]